Why is it so important for me to be an idol?
Welcome to the Zombieland Saga Project, baby!
We're gonna do the local idol thing?
We need a new name!
What do I do?
It's perfect fun!
Don't freak out. I'll be there to back you.
Whether or not you have what it takes is irrelevant because I do!
Can we go back to the way things were?
It was a crazy idea in the first place.
This project has a crucial deadline.
No doubt about it. All those girls are dead.
Hey, maybe he raised them from the dead like a bunch of zombies.
Uh...
Why am I smiling right now?
We can say, oh my God, that's neck and Eig gibi UP.
I'm young.
To be continued...
I betcha we can bring in a thousand people for the next show!
If we start getting cocky, then we're sure to make a mistake.
We should focus.
Work calmly and steadily.
Cool!
So I say we do that nerdy crap Junko just said,
and bring in that thousand!
Yeah!
If the movies have taught me anything,
it's that zombies with big fat heads are way easier to kill!
Look, if you brain-rotted suckers keep on riding the high from Arpino,
then it's BOOM!
Headshot!
Next show will be at Ekimai Furosan Stadium!
EFS if you're nasty!
Wait, I'm confused.
Where'd you say again?
What's wrong?
Yeah, I don't think I've ever heard of that venue before.
Eh, not like I care where they call the place.
Point is, we're putting a thousand butts in the seats this time.
Actually,
the name won't be changed until February.
I see somebody's done their homework.
Oh, no wonder it doesn't ring a bell.
So what's it called now?
The best amenity stadium.
The huge one in Tosu.
Uh, isn't that...
I promise I'll be okay.
The biggest issue is the size of the place.
I think the capacity is around...
25,000.
25,000?
That's like 50 Arpinos!
And with the field, there's standing room for even more.
If this thing goes south, could I take out that many people?
This is a really big deal.
There's no way we'll pull it off!
The concert is scheduled for March 8th.
Don't be an idiot!
A whole stadium here in Saga?
We could never fill it up!
Iron Frill did it back then, but...
So that was them then, and this is you now!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you knuckleheads honestly believe Iron Frill was better 10 years ago than you are today?
Because that is idiotic!
Your legends, each and every...
All except one of you, that is.
Don't single me out or anything.
I hand-selected you girls to come back to life and bring Saga to life, too!
You can accomplish anything!
So on March 8th, EFS will be jam-packed with your fans!
I say, get the crowd all fired up and encore with that new number!
Yeah!
This bomb is still lit!
Soon everyone will know Frans Choushu!
Shades is always drinking the dumbass juice, but even I can tell he chugged the whole bottle this time.
Is this really gonna work?
Normally, I'd say it's impossible.
You're right, it's just not realistic.
Yeah, but...
I know.
We're long past considering what's realistic.
Good point.
If Mr. Kotaro's really this dead set on it, maybe he's got a good reason we don't know about yet.
Doesn't he just pull stuff out of his butt?
I say... we try.
Huh?
Do you realize what a big risk this is?
I don't know if we'll be successful.
But if it's a chance for all of us to sing and dance together, then I'm more than up for it.
What matters to me is performing with you guys.
You're on.
You're right, the show Arpino is terrible.
And we made it through that.
Besides, everything that we do is bold and brazen.
Yeah, I mean, we're already zombies.
So it's not like this is gonna kill us, am I right?
Just listening to each of you talk makes me feel like we can actually do this.
I'm kind of shocked.
What am I gonna do with you crazies?
For this to work out, we need the show to be even better than Arpino.
If we do anything less than our best, then we're certain to fail.
Okay, now whip us into shape, I.
No problem.
Time to address everything I've been letting you guys slide on.
Mm-hmm.
Mostly you.
Uh, come on, don't be too mean.
What's wrong?
You can't handle it.
Ha!
Looks like there's still something bugging you.
Well, how could this not bug me?
It is where I died, after all.
You can't die twice.
No point in being scared.
I don't think you're the one to talk to since you jumped off the same cliff twice.
Hey, Ai.
Remember what you said back at the park?
I don't care if I'm a zombie.
I'm gonna get back on stage again.
And then I'll...
Let's make it happen.
If something goes wrong, I'll take care of it for us.
I'm the boss, and the boss can't be afraid to get her hands dirty.
Leader, not boss.
Same thing.
Huh?
Damn, that's scary!
I wanted to make sure you guys were okay.
Um, yeah.
It wasn't anything serious, sir.
We'll be fine.
I'll be there to back you up, too.
And I'm sorry for eavesdropping, but I couldn't help it.
I know!
We should have a rally to build up our morale!
We're idols, not bikers, Saki.
No, that isn't it.
There's no way we'll pull it off!
La, la, la, loo, la, loo, la...
That doesn't work.
This place is huge.
Question.
Hmm.
I was too nervous to ask before, but...
Would you mind telling me how many tickets we've sold so far?
I didn't print any.
Huh?
What did you say?
We're only selling them day of.
But why would you do that?
With this concert, we need to put out the message that Franshushu has risen in Saga.
That means it should be legendary in as many ways as possible.
Ordinary methods won't cut it.
Remember everything you've accomplished so far.
Believe in Franshushu, and believe in me as well.
Oh my gosh.
The whole crowd fits in the VIP area.
Um, hey guys.
Glad you're here.
We are, uh, Franshushu.
Come on.
Oh my gosh.
Should we yell for an encore?
No way, Chul.
Better be cruel.
Could this be the end?
Ladies, I'm home!
Oh look, if it isn't the legendary Fryster Pooh!
Mr. Kotaro, where were you?
We've been worried sick!
Don't you worry, baby Zed.
You know, your trusty old commander won't go MIA forever?
Don't tell me you were drinking all night.
Yeah, obviously.
Because guess what, girls?
We are drowning in debt now for about 20 mil.
Crazy, ain't it?
Yes, sirree.
We are 20 million dee.
We're in debt?
No, that can't be right.
No way.
I mean, yeah.
That was a large-scale concert and it failed tremendously.
Of course we're in debt.
Relax!
No use of crying now!
Front Shoo Shoo's done for!
Saga's done for too!
It's all done!
Let's pack it in, everybody!
Shades has been on his little bender for two whole weeks now.
And our food supply's been depleted for seven days.
Yeah, but zombies don't need to eat, so it's not that big of an issue, right?
Who knows?
Maybe he's coming up with an amazing plan to fix all this right now.
He's done it before, remember?
That asshat doesn't plan for crap!
That's how we ended up in this whole mess!
Hey, don't take your feelings out on Sakura.
You're not the only one who's irritated, you know.
Then I'll take him out on you!
Please don't fight, you two.
It's times like this we need to stick together.
We'll be okay somehow, even if he gives up on us.
You say that, but without Mr. Tatsumi's help, we can't do our makeup.
Which means we can't go shopping or anything either.
And the longer this goes on, the bigger our debt is going to get.
I'm sorry, Sakura, but it'll take a lot more than positivity to take care of this problem.
Tai?
Damn, your face looks busted.
She got that by herself?
I guess.
Which means she swiped his cash?
And painted her face?
Mm-hmm.
That's crazy.
This proves it.
We were wrong.
We can do anything if we try, just like Tai did.
The problem is, we haven't been trying our best.
We're so used to him calling the shots.
And with him gone, we assumed that we had to give up.
Yeah.
At some point, we started relying on him too much and took him for granted.
Right.
That's what happened with the EFS show.
All we thought was that if we do our best, he'll make everything else come together.
And clearly, that's not true.
Since we've got the makeup, guess we might as well use it.
Sounds fun, but how do we pay out the debt?
By working.
If we can't do idle stuff right now, then let's try to get part-time jobs until it's possible.
Cool.
Can I help out too?
Sure.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
We're good under pressure.
Time for us to do the thinking ourselves.
We can move forward without letting the past bring us down.
That's right.
In the end, I still happened.
What's up?
I'm in.
We may be zombies, but there's still life in us.
You're right.
Let's work hard so we can get our revenge.
That's a shame.
He's dead as dirt.
What's all that?
Just a bunch of squid?
Looks that way.
I'm not sure why, though.
He coughed!
Oh, he's alive!
You all right?
I'm better than ever.
Just got a little swept away is all.
And then the guy walked off!
Dude, how crazy is that?
We got ourselves a mysterious squid man.
I'll let you take that one.
What?
Well, your story must be pretty important, then.
I think even the Tokyo pubs are going to want this.
Oh, really?
Clock's ticking.
Right.
Gotcha.
Later, then, I got myself a squid man to track down.
Morning, ladies.
What happened to you?
Irrelevant.
Aren't you gonna—
One year ago, I made a big mistake.
On the last 8th of March, at my behest, you performed in a show that failed enormously.
I'm sorry.
That's why next month, you will return to EFS.
Your revenge show is March 8th.
Hey!
That said, the approach will be different.
I'm not just banking on our momentum.
This year, you've breathed new life into Franz Shushu.
Your album and merch sales have been plentiful, like the rice in the fields of Hanamura and Warabino.
More importantly, the seven of you have truly grown.
But despite all that, this show won't be easy.
Right now, I'm working on a variety of advertising projects to build up some hype.
I promise you girls, I'm giving this all I have.
Someday, when Franz Shushu is an even greater known legend, that failure will be a brief chapter in our tale.
That's why you picked March 8th.
Listen!
This battle will be fierce.
But take heart!
Because of your heroic act, Saga will be forever changed!
Even if Saga itself is plunged into darkness and despair, the seven of you will still remain!
A bright light, shining eternally throughout that pit of oblivion!
Never forget!
I hand-selected each of you to come back from the dead to become the new heroes of Saga!
And when your revenge is set into motion, that's the signal for Saga's counterattack to begin!
What's with the sneeze?
A little cold.
I thought it was cute.
That killed the whole thing!
Oh!
Shut up!
Kotaro Tatsumi, isn't it?
I'm Arata Okuba.
I write for Saga Zine.
Yeah.
I read your articles pretty often.
It's a shame what happened a year ago.
But it seems like your girls have been really outdoing themselves recently.
Are you here to reflect on past mistakes?
Sorry.
I'm not doing personal interviews.
You stay in my line of work long enough and you end up with acquaintances all over the place.
That said, it took me a while to connect the dots this time.
Sakura Minamoto, Saki Nikaido, Ai Mizuno, Miss Junko Kono, Lily Hoshikawa slash Masao Go, and Tai Yamada.
All of those people are dead.
Sadly, I wasn't able to dig up any until about number five.
Heh.
You ready to talk?
What exactly are these women?
These pictures beg a lot of questions.
I can have their graves exhumed, you know.
Why write something like this?
Because I feel compelled to stop you from trying to profit off these poor deceased girls by turning them into singing and dancing clowns.
Is that reason enough for you?
Feel free to stay silent.
But after the article is published, your big secret will be out.
It's shocking news.
I wonder what the public will think.
They'll be here next month, performing in a big concert.
What?
It's their revenge.
You're insane.
Why would you want to recreate such a disaster?
How dare you turn the dead into cheap entertainment?
You can publish anything you like, but you'll never stop Franshu Shuu.
I'll make sure they don't take that stage.
You okay down there?
The high school girl kept her mouth shut, but I doubt it'll work out that way this time.
Though if I'm being honest, I was a little surprised that the word didn't get out sooner.
And the reporter's not your only problem.
Things have been rough lately, but this'll be worse than some scratches and stolen clothes.
I don't care about that crap.
This show is gonna be a roaring success.
I won't screw up again.
Hm. Twelve years ago, when I first ran into that gloomy half-crazed kid, I never thought he could make all of this happen.
If I wasn't gloomy and half-crazed, then I doubt I would have believed you.
That you're immortal, fighting a curse that's been at work in Saga for centuries.
And that part about how you can revive the dead.
Hm. But you got what you wanted.
Not yet.
I still have to find a way to stop your prophecy from coming true.
As the Rewa era starts, Saga will face a cataclysmic threat.
A powerful phenomenon will cause thoughts of Saga to disappear,
and even memories of Saga's past will be lost forever.
Of course, things were already looking dire enough with the population decreasing.
Exactly. So the obvious solution was to create something in Saga that's impossible to forget.
Gathering young women killed by the curse who otherwise would have brought glory to this region,
and making them into a popular idol group that the people of Saga can be proud of?
I admit, it's a great idea, this Mount Mifuneyama Rakuin project of yours.
It's called the Zombieland Saga Project.
That's what I meant.
The world is shaped by the actions of men.
You're wrong there.
Men and zombies.
It's both, hand in hand.
All of Kyushu is under a severe rain warning tonight and into tomorrow morning.
That's a lot of rain.
I wonder if Kokoro's okay?
He'll be fine.
I sure hope so.
When he gets back, we ought to blast him with the waterproof spray.
Tomorrow's when our badass revenge officially starts.
We should probably get some rest.
Yeah.
Kay, done.
This sure has been a hell of an article to write.
Next month, they'll be doing a concert here.
You can't dishonor the dead like that, I'll show him!
What the hell?
Are you kidding me?
Mm-hmm.
This is it.
Get ready!
Junko here. There's still a lot to be anxious about, but it would take a total catastrophe to stop us from at least giving it our best.
Next time, Zombieland Saga Revenge Episode 11. All it takes is for you to be there, Saga. See you then!